If no command is provided, haeng will try to
download all currently saved playlists.

Usage: haeng.exe [COMMAND]

Commands:
  add
          Add a YouTube playlist
  remove
          Remove a YouTube playlist
  download
          Download a specific playlist
  view
          View all playlists currently tracked
  help
          Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)

Options:
  -h, --help
          Print help (see a summary with '-h')
